let's look at the solution for our
laundry pipelining quiz we have a washer
dryer and folder each takes one hour we
have 10 loads of laundry with no
pipelining
one load takes three hours to finish
only then we begin the next load so it's
gonna take 30 hours to do them because
we do them one at a time each takes
three hours with pipelining the first
load will take one to three hours so so
far we are no better off however once
the first load is in the folder the
second load is already in the dryer when
the first load leaves the pipeline after
three hours it takes only one hour to do
the folding for the next load so we have
after the initial three hours one load
leaving every hour so what we have
really is three hours for the first load
plus one hour for the remaining loads
overall it takes only 12 hours to
process the 10 loads as you can see
pipelining can significantly prove the
execution time when we have many things
to do and when you have instructions you
usually have a lot of them to do